<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

  <channel>
    <title>ClaimTek Systems</title>
    <atom:link href="https://www.claimtek.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <link>https://www.claimtek.net</link>
    <description></description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 02:11:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
    <sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
    <generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.0.3</generator>

    <image>
      <url>https://www.claimtek.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/ctsl.png</url>
      <title>ClaimTek Systems</title>
      <link>https://www.claimtek.net</link>
      <width>32</width>
      <height>32</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Live &#038; Private One-On-One Training from the comfort of your home</title>
      <link>https://www.claimtek.net/training/training-one-on-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 10:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator><![CDATA[amir@claimteksystems.com]]></dc:creator>
      <category><![CDATA[Training]]></category>

      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.claimtek.net/?p=22</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Professional Online One-On-One Training In The Comfort Of Your Home! It&#8217;s one-on-one, personable, comprehensive, cost saving and ongoing. Training is scheduled around your hours and available 7 days a week. Stay home, relax and enjoy the most effective Medical Billing training on the planet! Avoid travel expenses and seminar distractions. Learn One-On-One! You&#8217;ll have undivided]]></description>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<div class="row row-edge  " >
<div class="col-md-12">
<h3>Professional Online One-On-One Training In The Comfort Of Your Home!</h3>
<h4>It&#8217;s one-on-one, personable, comprehensive, cost saving and ongoing. Training is scheduled around your hours and available 7 days a week.</h4>
<p>Stay home, relax and enjoy the most effective Medical Billing training on the planet! Avoid travel expenses and seminar distractions. Learn One-On-One! You&#8217;ll have undivided attention from a professional personal mentor!</p>
<p>In addition to our extensive medical billing training material (manuals, audio, video &#8212; as detailed on the other tabs in this section), ClaimTek offers a completely personalized one-on-one medical billing training program.</p>
<blockquote><p>The training is divided into three stages</p></blockquote>
</div>
</div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div class="row row-edge  " >
<div class="col-md-12 col-xs-offset-0 col-sm-offset-0 col-md-offset-0 col-lg-offset-0 col-xs-pull-0 col-sm-pull-0 col-md-pull-0 col-lg-pull-0 col-xs-push-0 col-sm-push-0 col-md-push-0 col-lg-push-0">
<a class="cherry-btn cherry-btn-primary cherry-btn-medium cherry-btn-inline cherry-btn-fade  " target="_self" href="http://www.claimtek.com/Training/Default.aspx">See Details On Our Information Bank Website</a>
</div>
</div>
]]>
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Stage One, Live Exercises</title>
      <link>https://www.claimtek.net/training/training-stage-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 10:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator><![CDATA[amir@claimteksystems.com]]></dc:creator>
      <category><![CDATA[Training]]></category>

      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.claimtek.net/?p=18</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[We Teach You Every Step With Live Exercises You will be assigned a ClaimTek professional personal trainer (a mentor) to train you on our medical billing software, on medical billing fundamentals, and on marketing your new medical billing business. All this occurs while you sit in front of your computer in home office or at]]></description>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<div class="row row-edge  " >
<div class="col-md-12">
<h3>We Teach You Every Step With Live Exercises</h3>
<p>You will be assigned a ClaimTek professional personal trainer (a mentor) to train you on our medical billing software, on medical billing fundamentals, and on marketing your new medical billing business. All this occurs while you sit in front of your computer in home office or at your business office. Our medical billing business training is conducted using state-of-the-art interactive online training platform. Training is performed in private one-on-one sessions ranging from 1-2 hours per session. Your mentor will assign homework between sessions. Depending on the program you choose, you can receive up to 28 hours of focused one-on-one medical billing training which, in reality, amounts to over 200 hours! Our take-you-by-the-hand approach is highly effective because you will receive personal guidance from a professional medical billing trainer manager. The training is conducted with no interruptions or distractions from other people as so often happens in a large group training session. Your personal training is completely tailored to your needs and to your level of knowledge with computers.</p>
<p>Training on the marketing aspects of the medical billing business is vital at this initial stage. We cover topics from the basic steps to advanced techniques that give your new business the exposure it needs. We include a blow-by-blow marketing schedule of marketing steps and a guide on how to use every marketing item that comes with the package. We provide you with an effective telephone script for appointment setting, rebuttal scripts, and an appointment suggestion script (DOs and DON&#8217;Ts).</p>
<p>This medical billing training method is efficient and convenient. You do not need to pay the cost of travel and lodging expenses as some programs require you to do. Furthermore, you will not find yourself being trained in a noisy group where the topics are skimmed over and training is often interrupted by frivolous questions from the group. Profit from the one-on-one ClaimTek medical billing training! Learn and practice on your own computer at convenient times from the comfort of your own home! Learn claims transmission and the file transfer methods that you&#8217;ll be using daily in your business.</p>
<blockquote><p>Stages 2 and 3 below are referred to as the &#8220;Business Consulting, Training, and Coaching</p></blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h4>(BCTC) package. BCTC is designed to give you excellent ongoing training and peace of mind as you grow your business.</h4>
</div>
</div>
<div class="row row-edge  " >
<div class="col-md-12 col-xs-offset-0 col-sm-offset-0 col-md-offset-0 col-lg-offset-0 col-xs-pull-0 col-sm-pull-0 col-md-pull-0 col-lg-pull-0 col-xs-push-0 col-sm-push-0 col-md-push-0 col-lg-push-0">
<a class="cherry-btn cherry-btn-info cherry-btn-large cherry-btn-inline cherry-btn-fade  " target="_self" href="http://www.claimtek.com/Training/Default.aspx"><span class="fa fa-info-circle cherry-btn-icon icon-position-left icon-882"></span><span class="cherry-btn-content-wrap">See Full Details ON Our Information Bank Website</span></a>
</div>
</div>
]]>
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Stage Two, Be Prepared</title>
      <link>https://www.claimtek.net/training/article-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 10:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator><![CDATA[amir@claimteksystems.com]]></dc:creator>
      <category><![CDATA[Training]]></category>

      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.claimtek.net/?p=21</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[&#160;]]></description>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<div class="row row-edge  " >
<div class="col-md-12">
<h3>Pre-Appointment Training And Consulting Sessions!</h3>
<h4>personal consulting</h4>
<p>The second stage is a &#8220;personal consulting&#8221; stage for any upcoming appointments you set. This stage is where your trainer/mentor prepares you for the appointment concerning what kind of questions you may expect from a specific specialty or clinic, what types of issues to discuss (specific to the specialty). And also, what your pricing strategy may look like. This last item is important as your pricing may differ from one medical practice account to another depending on several factors, like the type of specialty, office size, services offered&#8230;etc.</p>
<p>It is important for you to impress the doctor/office manager with your knowledge and skills during the interview. You need to be as prepared as if you were going to a job interview. The more you know about your prospect, the better your presentation will be.</p>
<blockquote><p>We&#8217;ll Prepare You For Battle</p></blockquote>
</div>
</div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div class="row row-edge  " >
<div class="col-md-12 col-xs-offset-0 col-sm-offset-0 col-md-offset-0 col-lg-offset-0 col-xs-pull-0 col-sm-pull-0 col-md-pull-0 col-lg-pull-0 col-xs-push-0 col-sm-push-0 col-md-push-0 col-lg-push-0">
<a class="cherry-btn cherry-btn-primary cherry-btn-medium cherry-btn-inline cherry-btn-fade  " target="_self" href="http://www.claimtek.com/Training/Default.aspx"><span class="fa fa-info-circle cherry-btn-icon icon-position-left icon-681"></span><span class="cherry-btn-content-wrap">See Full Details On Our Information Bank Website</span></a>
</div>
</div>
]]>
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Stage Three, We Team-Up With You</title>
      <link>https://www.claimtek.net/training/training-stage-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 10:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator><![CDATA[amir@claimteksystems.com]]></dc:creator>
      <category><![CDATA[Training]]></category>

      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.claimtek.net/?p=20</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<div class="row row-edge  " >
<div class="col-md-12">
<h3>FREE Consulting Sessions When You Sign Up Clients!</h3>
<p>The third stage takes place when you sign up your first account. Here, your trainer will give you a free refresher course on the software and also on the billing aspects for the specialty you just signed up. Your trainer will make sure all signup procedures are handled properly, will help you set up your client&#8217;s database, and also oversee the first transmission of claims to the clearinghouse. This great service is provided to you FREE!</p>
<blockquote><p>With You Along The Way!</p></blockquote>
<p>We take the trouble to work with you through these three stages because no one can simply learn every important aspect of the medical billing business at once. ClaimTek provides you with ongoing &#8220;consulting support&#8221; in addition to &#8220;technical support&#8221;. &#8220;Consulting support&#8221; is where you get to discuss specific issues with your trainer at length. This includes the vital issues of pricing strategies and any demands of the medical specialty at hand. No other company in this business provides the quality and comprehensive level of support as ClaimTek. As you might think, this kind of training process is clearly the most effective and helps you get started with confidence. Coupled with our world-class support you&#8217;ll go into the market with a solid training and support foundation to build on.</p>
<p>We hope that you will compare our extensive medical billing training carefully with that of other companies who offer medical billing software and training only once per month (or worse) and in a large classroom setting. Once you are trained in a classroom with them, you&#8217;ll hardly ever get any refresher courses or a chance to speak at length with an expert trainer. Your entire business venture depends on the tech support department where you get answers to your technical questions only. Some companies may offer telephone training but limit it to &#8220;software training only.&#8221; ClaimTek&#8217;s 3-stage medical billing training is the only one that maximizes your chances for the level of comprehensive knowledge that allows you a solid entry in the medical billing business.</p>
<p>Our marketing campaign materials and support are just as detailed as the training. We provide comprehensive and effective tools for a successful medical billing marketing campaign. After studying the training section, please visit our marketing section to learn more.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="row row-edge  " >
<div class="col-md-12 col-xs-offset-0 col-sm-offset-0 col-md-offset-0 col-lg-offset-0 col-xs-pull-0 col-sm-pull-0 col-md-pull-0 col-lg-pull-0 col-xs-push-0 col-sm-push-0 col-md-push-0 col-lg-push-0">
<a class="cherry-btn cherry-btn-primary cherry-btn-medium cherry-btn-inline cherry-btn-fade  " target="_self" href="http://www.claimtek.com/Training/Default.aspx"><span class="fa fa-info-circle cherry-btn-icon icon-position-left icon-649"></span><span class="cherry-btn-content-wrap">See Full Details On Our Information Bank Website</span></a>
</div>
</div>
]]>
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>